Prathamesh Netake

Panvel, Navi Mumbai. +91-9082199961 prathamesh.netake@gmail.com prathameshnetake.github.io

Full Stack JavaScript developer with extensive experience in web and product development. Aiming to use my proven skills in ReactJS and Node.js to effectively fill the Senior Software Engineer role at your company. Possess a Bachelors in Engineering in Computer Engineering.

Experience

JUNE 2018 - PRESENT

Product Lead / AitoeLabs, Mumbai

Led a team of front-end and back-end developers to design and build boiler-plates and custom UI products, as per the project requirements.

NOV 2017 - PRESENT

Senior Software Engineer/ AitoeLabs, Mumbai

Designed and developed an end-to-end UI application for multiple surveillance products using technologies such as ReactJS, Node.js and MongoDB.

JAN 2016 - JUNE 2017

Software Developer/Zeus Learning, Mumbai

Developed various e-learning tools using MVC frameworks such as Angular 4 and Backbone for multinational clients. Designed and fabricated the website of Zeus Learning.

Education

JUNE 2016

Bachelor of Engineering / University of Mumbai

Majored in Computer Engineering. Google Student Ambassador. Developed Websites for Committees.

Skills

- React.JS
- CSS3, SCSS, Stylus
- Vue.JS

- Node.js
- AngularJS, Angular
- BackBone.js

For more information visit prathameshnetake.github.io (Portfolio website)